Guide to the Jean Kilbourne Papers, 1918-2014 and undated RL.10982
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Printed Materials, 1933-2014; 1; 5 boxes
  - You Just Don't Understand: Women and Men in Conversation. Deborah Tennen, Ph.D. William Morrow and Company, Inc. English., 1990 (Box PM2)
  - A New Man. Luke Reynolds. StoneGarden.net Publishing. English., 2007 (Box PM3)
  - A Preaching Ministry. Harry Emerson Fosdick. The First Presbyterian Church in the City of New York. English., 2000 (Box PM3)
  - Body Shots: Hollywood and the Culture of Eating Disorders. Emily Fox-Kales. State University of New York Press. English., 2011 (Box PM3)
  - Cartographies of Desire: Captivity, Race, and Sex in the Shaping of an American Nation. Rebecca Blevins Faery. University of Oklahoma Press. English., 1999 (Box PM3)
  - Consuming Innocence: Popular Culture and Our Children. Karen Brooks. University of Queensland Press. English., 2008 (Box PM3)
  - Does Advertising Promote Substance Abuse? Lori M. Newman, Editor. Greenhaven Press. English., 2005 (Box PM3)
  - Drink: The Intimate Relationship Between Women and Alcohol. Ann Dowsett Johnston. Harper Wave. English., 2013 (Box PM3)
  - Edgar Allan Poe in Albanian Literature (Translated from Romanian). Luljeta Krasniqi. Botimet Toena [?]. Albanian., 2007 (Box PM3)
  - Families Like Mine: Children of Gay Parents Tell it Like it is. Abigail Garner. HarperCollins. English., 2004 (Box PM3)
  - From Hardtack to Home Fries: An Uncommon History of American Cooks and Meals. Barbara Haber. The Free Press. English., 2002 (Box PM3)
  - Hey, Kidz! Buy This Book: A Radical Primer on Corporate and Governmental Propaganda and Artistic Activism for Short People. Anne Elizabeth Moore. Soft Skull Press. English., 2004 (Box PM3)
  - I Thought it Was Just Me: Women Reclaiming Power and Courage in a Culture of Shame. Brene Brown, Ph.D., L.M.S.W. Gotham Books. English., 2007 (Box PM3)
  - Image in Advertising: Verbal and Visual Coded of Commerce. Fern L. Johnson. Routledge. English., 2008 (Box PM3)
  - Losing It: False Hopes and Fat Profits in the Diet Industry. Laura Fraser. Plume Books. English., 1997 (Box PM3)
  - Maiden USA: Girl Icons Come of Age. Kathleen Sweeney. Peter Lang. English., 2008 (Box PM3)
  - Not So Typical After All. Keith Murfee. Lulu Enterprises Inc. English., 2004 (Box PM3)
  - Of Face Value. Carol Harper. Publish America. English., 2006 (Box PM3)
  - Race/ Gender/ Media: Considering Diversity across Audiences, Content, and Producers. Rebecca Ann Lind. Allyn and Bacon. English., 2004 (Box PM3)
  - Race/ Gender/ Media: Considering Diversity across Audiences, Content, and Producers. Rebecca Ann Lind. Allyn and Bacon. English., 2004 (Box PM3)
  - Real Kids Come in all Sizes: 10 Essential Lessons to Build Your Child's Body Esteem. Kathy Kater. Broadway Books. English., 2004 (Box PM3)
  - Screaming to be Heard: Hormonal Connections Women Suspect--and Doctors Ignore. Elizabeth Lee Vliet, M.D. M. Evans and Company. English., 1995 (Box PM3)
  - Sex in Advertising: Perspectives on the Erotic Appeal. Edited by: Tom Reichert and Jacqueline Lambiase. Lawrence Erlbaum Associates, Publishers. English., 2003 (Box PM3)
  - Someday is Here!: Thirty Days to Personal Renewal, Spiritual Growth and Enhanced Creativity. Jeanette Isabella. Venture Press. English., 1997 (Box PM3)
  - Spiritual Concupiscence': John Cotton's English Years, 1584-1633. Jesper Rosenmeier. Richard Kay Publications. English., 2012 (Box PM3)
  - Still Sexy After All These Years?: The 9 Unspoken Truths About Women's Desire Beyond 50. Leah Kliger, MHA and Deborah Nedelman, Ph.D. Perigee Books. English., 2006 (Box PM3)
  - The 80% Minority: Reaching the Real World of Women. Joanne Thomas Yaccato. Viking Canada. English., 2003 (Box PM3)
  - The American Paradox: Spiritual Hunger in an Age of Plenty. David G. Myers. Yale University Press. English., 2000 (Box PM3)
  - The Mirror Makers: A History of American Advertising and Its Creators. Stephen Fox. William Morrow and Company, Inc. English., 1984 (Box PM3)
  - The Mother-Daughter Project: How Mothers and Daughters Can Band Together, Beat the Odds, and Thrive Through Adolescence. Sue Ellen Hamkins, MD, and Renee Schultz, MA. Hudson Street Press. English., 2007 (Box PM3)
  - The Power of Partnership: Seven Relationships That Will Change Your Life. Riane Eisler. New World Library. English., 2002 (Box PM3)
  - The Real Wealth of Nations: Creating a Caring Economy. Riane Eisler. Berrett-Koehler Publications. English., 2007 (Box PM3)
  - The Secret Sales Pitch. August Bullock, attorney at law. Norwich Publishers. English., 2004 (Box PM3)
  - Video Games and Your Kids: How Parents Stay in Control. Hilarie Cash, PhD and Kim McDaniel, MA. Idyall Arbor Inc. English., 2008 (Box PM3)
  - WomanHours: A 21-Day Time Management Plan That Works. Gretchen Hirsch. St. Martin's Press. English., 1983 (Box PM3)
  - 20 Years of Censored News. Carl Jensen. Seven Stories Press. English., 1997 (Box PM4)
  - A Woman's Book of Strength: An Empowering Guide to Total Mind/Body Fitness. Karen Andes. Perigee Books. English., 1995 (Box PM4)
  - Adproofing Your Kids: Raising Critical Thinkers in a Media-Saturated World. Tania Andrusiak and Daniel Donahoo. Finch Publishing Sydney. English., 2009 (Box PM4)
  - Advertising and Social Change. Ronald Berman. SAGE Publications. English., 1981 (Box PM4)
  - An Ethics Trajectory: Visions of Media Past, Present and Yet to Come. Thomas W. Cooper, Clifford G. Christians and Anantha S. Babbili. The Institute of Communications Research at the University of Illinois. English., 2008 (Box PM4)
  - An Ethics Trajectory: Visions of Media Past, Present and Yet to Come. Thomas W. Cooper, Clifford G. Christians and Anantha S. Babbili. The Institute of Communications Research at the University of Illinois. English., 2008 (Box PM4)
  - Anger Antidotes: How Not to Lose Your S#&!. Ian Brennan. W.W. Norton and Company. English., 2011 (Box PM4)
  - Anything she can do I can do Better: The Truth About Female Competition. Rachael Oakes-Ash. Random House Australia. English., 2003 (Box PM4)
  - Branded: The Buying and Selling of Teenagers. Alissa Quart. Perseus Publishing. English., 2003 (Box PM4)
  - Breasts: The Women's Perspective on an American Obsession. Carolyn Latteier. Harrington Park Press. English., 1998 (Box PM4)
  - Caught Looking: Feminism, Pornography and Censorship. Caught Looking Inc. The Real Comet Press. English., 1988 (Box PM4)
  - Getting Real: Challenging the Sexualisation of Girls. Edited by Melinda Tankard Reist. Spinifex Press. English., 2009 (Box PM4)
  - How to Say it to Girls: Communicating with Your Growing Daughter. Nancy Gruver. Prentice Hall Press. English., 2004 (Box PM4)
  - Icons of Popular Culture. Marshall Fishwick and Ray B. Browne. Bowling Green University Popular Press. English., 1970 (Box PM4)
  - In Your Face: The Culture of Beauty and You. Shari Graydon. Annick Press. English., 2004 (Box PM4)
  - Lives Together, Worlds Apart: Mothers and Daughters in Popular Culture. Suzanna Danuta Walters. University of California Press. English., 1992 (Box PM4)
  - Living More With Less. Doris Janzen Longacre. Herald Press. English., 1980 (Box PM4)
  - Menopause: A Self-care Manual. Judy Costlow, Maria Cristina Lopez and Mara Taub. Santa Fe Health Education Project. English., 1989 (Box PM4)
  - Mother Daughter Choices: A Handbook for the Coordinator. Girls Incorporated of Greater Santa Barbara. Advocacy Press. English., 1988 (Box PM4)
  - Nourishing Your Daughter: Help Your Child Develop a Healthy Relationship with Food and Drink. Carol Beck. Perigee Books. English., 2001 (Box PM4)
  - On Earth as it is in Advertising? Sam Van Eman. Brazos Press. English., 2005 (Box PM4)
  - Preference Pollution: How Markets Create the Desires we Dislike. David George. University of Michigan Press. English., 2001 (Box PM4)
  - Raising Strong Daughters. Jeanette Gadeberg. Fairview Press. English., 1995 (Box PM4)
  - Speaking and Listening from the Heart. Linda Wolf with Neva Welton. Dsistas Press. English., 2005 (Box PM4)
  - Talking Back to Facebook: The Common Sense Guide to Raising Kids in the Digital Age. James P. Steyer. Scribner. English., 2012 (Box PM4)
  - The Change: Women, Aging and the Menopause. Germaine Greer. Fawcett Columbine. English., 1991 (Box PM4)
  - The Culture and Politics of Breastfeeding. Naomi Baumslag and Dia L Michels. The Other India Press. English., 1995 (Box PM4)
  - The Mass Market Woman: Defining Yourself as a Person in a World That Defines You By Your Appearance. Linda McBryde, M.D. Crowded Hour Press. English., 1999 (Box PM4)
  - The Menopause Self Help Book: A Woman's Guide to Feeling Wonderful for the Second Half of Her Life. Susan M. Lark, M.D. Celestial Arts. English., 1990 (Box PM4)
  - Things Will be Different for My Daughter: A Practical Guide to Building Her Self-Esteem and Self-Reliance. Mindy Bingham and Sandy Stryker. Penguin Books. English., 1995 (Box PM4)
  - Will the Last Reporter Please Turn out the Lights: The Collapse of Journalism and What can be Done to Fix it. Edited by Robert W. McChesney and Victor Pickard. The New Press. English., 2001 (Box PM4)
  - Winning the Image Game: A Ten Step Masterplan for Achieving Power, Prestige and Profit. Bobbie Gee. Page Mill Press. English., 1991 (Box PM4)
  - You Have to say I'm Pretty, You're my Mother: How to Help Your Daughter Learn to Love Her Body and Herself. Stephanie Pierson and Phyllis Cohen, CSW. Simon and Schuster. English., 2003 (Box PM5)
  - Backlash: The Undeclared War Against American Women. Susan Faludi. Crown Publishers Inc. English., 1991 (Box PM5)
  - Hear Us, Large Corporations!: Lessons From Kids and Adults to Corporate and Governmental Entities. Edited by: Anne Elizabeth Moore, Ed. Non Given. English., 2004 (Box PM5)
  - Marketing Madness: A Survival Guide for a Consumer Society. Michael F. Jacobson, Laurie Ann Mazur. Westview Press. English., 1995 (Box PM5)
  - Packaging Boyhood: Saving our Sons From Superheroes, Slackers, and Other Media Stereotypes. Lun Mikel Brown, ED.D., Sharon Lamb, ED.D., and Mark Tappan, ED.D. St. Martin's Press. English., 2009 (Box PM5)
  - Revolution From Within. Gloria Steinem. Little, Brown and Company. English., 1992 (Box PM5)
  - Box of note cards relating to sexism and media, undated (Box PM5)
  - American Plastic: Boob Jobs, Credit Cards, and Our Quest for Perfection. Laurie Essig. 2010: Beacon Press (Box PM6)
  - Alcohol Advertising: A Call for Congressional Action. Jean Kilbourne, 1988. (Box PM6)
  - Adolescent Girls and Smoking. National Women's Health Report. 2001 (Box PM6)
  - Mexican postcards, undated (Box PM6)
- Slides and Slide Presentations, 1977-2002 and undated; 14 boxes
  - Addiction/Values, undated; 3 folders (Box 89)
  - Advertising/Addiction/Breasts, undated (Box 89)
  - Advertising archives, undated (Box 89)
  - Advertising archives/Cartoons/Parodies, undated (Box 89)
  - Advertising--Gender (AFTRA slide show), undated (Box 89)
  - Advertising--Marketing, undated (Box 89)
  - Advertising--The positioning era, undated (Box 89)
  - Advertising--Subliminal, undated; 3 folders (Box 89)
  - Aging, undated (Box 89)
  - Anti-sexism, 2002 and undated (Box 89)
  - Alcohol, undated; 3 folders (Box 89)
  - Alcohol, undated; 4 folders (Box 90)
  - Alcohol--Sex and romance, undated (Box 90)
  - Alcohol--Substance abuse, undated (Box 90)
  - Body parts and jeans, undated; 4 folders (Box 90)
  - Body parts and jeans, undated (Box 91)
  - Cartoons, undated (Box 91)
  - Deadly Persuasion, undated; 3 folders (Box 91)
  - Drugs--Marketing, undated (Box 91)
  - Drugs--Other, undated (Box 91)
  - Drugs--Over the counter (OTC), undated (Box 91)
  - Drugs--Parodies, undated (Box 91)
  - Drugs--Prescription, undated (Box 91)
  - Food and diet (by theme), undated; 4 folders (Box 91)
  - Marketing (by theme), undated (Box 91)
  - Marketing (by theme), undated; 4 folders (Box 92)
  - Men/Positive ads/Miscellaneous, undated; 4 folders (Box 92)
  - Men/Dismemberment, undated (Box 92)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 92)
  - PL archives, undated (Box 92)
  - Sex, undated (Box 93)
  - Sexual Health [?--SH], undated; 2 folders (Box 93)
  - Sexualizing children, undated (Box 93)
  - Stereotypes/Sexual Sell, undated; 4 folders (Box 93)
  - Subliminal/Co-opting relationship, undated (Box 93)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT], undated; 2 folders (Box 93)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT], undated; 3 folders (Box 94)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT]--Archives current, undated; 2 folders (Box 94)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT]--Classics from early version, undated (Box 94)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT]--Early version, undated (Box 94)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT]--Image/Minorities, undated; 3 folders (Box 94)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT]--Image/Minorities, undated (Box 95)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT]--Little girls/children, undated; 4 folders (Box 95)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT]--Mothers/work, undated; 3 folders (Box 95)
  - The Naked Truth [TNT]--Violence, undated; 4 folders (Box 95)
  - Tobacco, undated; 3 folders (Box 96)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes by theme, undated; 4 folders (Box 96)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Women, by theme, undated; 3 folders (Box 97)
  - Tobacco--Cigars, undated (Box 97)
  - Tobacco--Smokeless tobacco, undated (Box 97)
  - Under the Influence (UI)--Alcohol, by theme, undated; 3 folders (Box 97)
  - Under the Influence (UI)--Alcohol, by theme, undated; 3 folders (Box 98)
  - Under the Influence (UI)--Archives, undated (Box 98)
  - Under the Influence (UI)--Archives, undated; 2 folders (Box 99)
  - Under the Influence (UI)--Consider from face, undated (Box 99)
  - Under the Influence (UI)--Sex, by theme, undated; 2 folders (Box 99)
  - Values/Relationships, undated (Box 99)
  - Violence, undated (Box 99)
  - Violence--Positive ads, undated (Box 99)
  - Violet Ray's ads, undated (Box 99)
  - Women, undated; 2 folders (Box 99)
  - Women, undated; 2 folders (Box 100)
  - Women--Aggressive women, undated (Box 100)
  - Women--Aggressive women/cooptation/body language, undated; 4 folders (Box 100)
  - Women--Co-optation, undated (Box 100)
  - Women--Dismemberment, undated (Box 100)
  - Women--Ideal image, undated (Box 100)
  - Women--Working women, undated (Box 100)
  - Slide presentations, undated (Box 100)
    - Alcohol Advertising and Women, undated (Box 100)
    - Alcohol Availability in an Public Health Perspective (Mosher & Coleman, San Francisco General Hospital), undated (Box 100)
    - Alcohol Policy: A Public Health Perspective (Trauma Foundation, San Francisco, Calif.), undated (Box 101)
    - Alcohol Policy Slide Set Series, 1997; 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Current titles and stats, undated (Box 101)
    - Face slides and other information, undated (Box 101)
    - Following Imaginary Peers: How Norm Misperceptions Influence Student Substance Use (Wisconsin Clearinghouse), undated (Box 101)
    - Great Expectations: Alcohol Advertising (Alcoholism Council of Nebraska), 1993 (Box 101)
    - Images About Alcohol (Mid State Substance Abuse Commission), 1993 (Box 101)
    - Obesity AAP, undated (Box 101)
    - Old stat and title slides, 1982-1992 (Box 101)
    - Public policy workshop, undated (Box 101)
    - RJR's Joe Camel Campaign (STAT), 1992 (Box 102)
    - Selling Alcohol to Latinos and African Americans (Lie, Cheat and Steal; Pura Vida? Pura Mentira!) (Box 102)
    - Sex and Substance Abuse: What Are the Links? (Wisconsin Clearinghouse), undated (Box 102)
    - Slides used on TV show, undated (Box 102)
    - STAT (Stop Teenage Addiction to Tobacco) Speaker's Guide and Slide Collection, undated; 2 folders (Box 102)
    - STAT Spit Tobacco Speaker's Guide, 1996 (Box 102)
    - STAT--The Tobacco Industry's Targeting of Women and People of Color, 1994 (Box 103)
    - Writing and media slides, 1977 and undated (Box 103)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1970-2006 and undated; 9; 11 boxes
  - RL10982-VHS-0001. 2014-0217. The Ad And The Ego. Review copy. TRT: 58:00. VHS. Original. Undated., 1824-1846 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0002. 2014-0217. The Ad And The Ego. TRT 57:00. VHS. Original. 1996, 1847-1852 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0003. 2014-0217. Neil Postman- Into Your Classroom. TRT 50:00. VHS. Original. 1996, 1856 Sept.-1859 Dec. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0004. 2014-0217. Neil Postman- Into Your Classroom. TRT 50:00. VHS. Original. 1996, 1869-1873 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0005. 2014-0217. Pennsylvania Coalition against Rape/ National Sexual Violence Resource Center. Weeks 18-21. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0006. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0007. 2014-0217. Calling The Shots (2nd Revision). VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0008. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0009. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly: Advertising's Image of Women. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0010. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. TRT 32:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0011. 2014-0217. The Killing Screens: Media and the Culture of Violence. TRT 37:00. VHS. Original. 1994 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0012. 2014-0217. Pack of Lies: The Advertising of Tobacco. VHS. Original. 1992 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0013. 2014-0217. Just DO Media Literacy. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0014. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly 3: Advertising's Image of Women. TRT 34:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0015. 2014-0217. The Killing Screens: Media and the Culture of Violence. Old Version. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0016. 2014-0217. Alcohol TV commercials. Center for Science in the Public Interest. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0017. 2014-0217. Pack of Lies: The Advertising of Tobacco. Preview. VHS. Original. 1992 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0018. 2014-0217. Excerpts from The Killing Screen. TRT 9:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0019. 2014-0217. The Killing Screens: Media and the Culture of Violence. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0020. 2014-0217. The Killing Screens: Media and the Culture of Violence. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0021. 2014-0217. Pack of Lies: The Advertising of Tobacco. Preview. VHS. Original. 1992 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0022. 2014-0217. Jean on Oprah. Copy. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0023. 2014-0217. Spin The Bottle- Media. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0024. 2014-0217. 10 Minutes of J Kilbourne. Original Lecture. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0025. 2014-0217. Pack of Lies: The Advertising of Tobacco. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0026. 2014-0217. Jean on Oprah. Copy. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0027. 2014-0217. Slim Hopes. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0028. 2014-0217. Slim Hopes. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0029. 2014-0217. Slim Hopes: Advertising and the Obsession With Thinness. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0030. 2014-0217. Prime for Life. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0031. 2014-0217. Daughters/Sisters Promo 1. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0032. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly 3: Advertising's Image of Women. TRT 34:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0033. 2014-0217. Deadly Persuasion: The Advertising of Alcohol and Tobacco. TRT 55:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0034. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly 3: Advertising's Image of Women. TRT 34:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV1)
  - RL10982-VHS-0035. 2014-0217. Advertising Alcohol: Calling the Shots. 2nd Edition. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0036. 2014-0217. Advertising Alcohol: Calling the Shots. Updated Version. VHS. Original. 1991 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0037. 2014-0217. Advertising Alcohol: Calling the Shots. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0038. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0039. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0040. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly: Advertising's Image of Women. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0041. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly: Advertising's Image of Women. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0042. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly: Advertising's Image of Women. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0043. 2014-0217. Advertising Alcohol: Calling the Shots. Updated Version. VHS. Original. 1991 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0044. 2014-0217. Advertising Alcohol: Calling the Shots. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0045. 2014-0217. The Naked Truth: Advertising's Image of Women. VHS. Original. 1984 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0046. 2014-0217. Under the Influence. VHS. Original. 1984 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0047. 2014-0217. Advertising Alcohol: Calling the Shots. Updated Version. VHS. Original. 1991 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0048. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly. TRT 29:12. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0049. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. VHS. Original. 1987 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0050. 2014-0217. Once Upon a Loss. VHS. Original. 1995 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0051. 2014-0217. Advertising Alcohol: Calling the Shots. Updated Version. VHS. Original. 1991 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0052. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0053. 2014-0217. Dreamworlds: Deisre, Sex, Power in Rock Video. VHS. Original. 1990 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0054. 2014-0217. Glimpses of Larry Kirkwood's Body Image Project. Extracted From his Lecure and Exhibit at the University of Wyoming. Feb 2002. VHS. Original. 2003 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0055. 2014-0217. Spin the Bottle: Sex, Lies and Alcohol. TRT 44:00. VHS. Original. 2004 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0056. 2014-0217. Deadly Persuasion: The Advertising of Alcohol and Tobacco. TRT 55:00. VHS. Original. 2003 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0057. 2014-0217. Deadly Persuasion: The Advertising of Alcohol and Tobacco. TRT 55:00. VHS. Original. 2003 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0058. 2014-0217. Once Upon a Loss: A New Look at Cinderella. For Preview Only. TRT 53:03. VHS. Original. 1994 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0059. 2014-0217. Spin the Bottle: Sex, Lies and Alcohol. TRT 44:00. VHS. Original. 2004 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0060. 2014-0217. Spin the Bottle: Sex, Lies and Alcohol. TRT 44:00. VHS. Original. 2004 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0061. 2014-0217. Spin the Bottle: Sex, Lies and Alcohol. TRT 44:00. VHS. Original. 2004 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0062. 2014-0217. Bell Hooks: Cultural Criticism and Transformation. TRT 66:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0063. 2014-0217. Reliving the Past: Alonzo Pond and the 1930 Logan African Expedition. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0064. 2014-0217. The Overspent American: Why We Want What We Don't Need. VHS. Original. 2003 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0065. 2014-0217. No Logo: Brands, Globalization, Resistance. VHS. Original. 2003 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0066. 2014-0217. Tough Guise: Violence, Media and the Crisis in Masculinity. TRT 82:00. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0067. 2014-0217. Tough Guise: Violence, Media and the Crisis in Masculinity. TRT 82:00. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV2)
  - RL10982-VHS-0068. 2014-0217. The Crisis of the Cultural Environment: Media and Democracy in the 21st Century. Preview Copy. TRT 26:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0069. 2014-0217. The Date Rape Backlash: The Media and Denial of Rape. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV3)